Okay, Halloween checklist.
I got my pumpkin carving knife,
I got my pumpkin scraping spoon,
and I got my super scary
pumpkin face design.
Ah!
I'm home!
I never left!
What you doin'?
I'm just gettin' ready
to turn a plain, old
everyday pumpkin into a serious,
butt-kickin' Jack-o'-lantern.
Ah. So where's Mr. Pumpkin?
Socko's bringin' one over.
Gotta love Socko.
Yup.
So, what are you doin'
for Halloween?
A very special "iCarly"
Halloween Webcast.
Appropriate.
What are you and Sam
gonna talk about?
You know,
all things Halloween-y.
Halloweeny.
Hey, look.
We got a letter addressed
to apartment 13-B.
Who lives in 13-B?
I don't know.
It says "occupant."
Well, then, just take it down
to the doorman.
Lewbert? Gross, no, eww.
He's not that bad.
Uh-huh, and his crazy
wart freaks me out.
Then just don't look at it.
Yeah, that's so possible.
It's like a big,
brown, hairy gumdrop.
You know, I had a dream
where it talked to me.
What did it say?
I don't know.
It only speaks Spanish.
Hey, can I have
a sip of your tea?
Sure...
But that's gasoline.
Kidding!
Aah!
I spent three weeks
making that for you!
All right, Mom, I'll wear it!
Gah!
I knew you'd laugh.
I'm not laughing.
Sometimes my lip just
quivers like this.
Uh-huh.
You just better take that off
before Sam sees you in it.
I can't take it off.
My mom made it for me,
and I promised her
I'd wear it tonight
while we do "iCarly."
Bummer for you.
Hey, I gotta take this letter
down to the lobby.
Wanna come?
Sure.
Okay, so, do you
wanna take the stairs,
or do you wanna fly us
there on your broom?
Nice.
I'm sorry!
Don't get mad
and turn me into a toad!
Carly!
I can't help it!
Socko, my bud,
you got the pumpkin?
Awesome. I got my carving knife
all ready to cut.
Just bring that
puppy on up here.
Oh, in the elevator?
Oh, how come
you're not comin' up?
Not enough room.
What do you mean
there's not enough room?
Oh, my God.
In five, four, three, two...
♪ I know you see ♪
♪ Somehow the world
will change for me ♪
♪ And be so wonderful ♪
♪ Live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow
we're going to get there ♪
♪ And feel so wonderful ♪
♪ It's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you
just how I feel ♪
♪ So wake up the members
of my nation ♪
♪ It's your time to breath ♪
♪ There's no chance
unless you take one ♪
♪ Every time you see
the brighter side ♪
♪ Of every situation ♪
♪ Some things
are meant to be ♪
♪ So give me your best
and leave the rest to me ♪
♪ Leave it all to me ♪
♪ Leave it all
to me ♪
♪ Just leave it all to me ♪
Hey, Lewbert, the mailman
put this letter
in our box by mistake.
Hey! Hey, boy.
What?
You makin' fun of me?
No. Why do you think
I'm making fun of...
What's with that fake
wart on your face?
You think warts are funny?
You think I'm happy
this thing grew here?
You think I like
that it has hair?
No.
My mom made this costume.
Well, she's sick!
You got a sick momma!
Um, if you could please
just give this letter
to whoever lives
in apartment 13-B?
Not possible!
No one's lived
in 13-B for 15 years.
But why would you keep
an apartment vacant
for 15 years?
'Cause the last
guy who lived there
said he heard noises,
saw strange things.
What?
You mean like ghosts?
I can't say no more!
But I...
I asked him a simple question
and he responded...
Hey, that lady's lived here
longer than anybody.
Why don't we ask her about 13-B?
'Kay.
Um, excuse me, ma'am.
I'm Carly Shay,
eighth floor, Capricorn.
I think her name's
Mrs. Halberstadt.
Mrs. Halberstadt,
we were wondering
if you knew anything
about apartment 13-B.
Hello?
Oh!
'Scuse me!
Okay, that was weird.
Something really bad
must have happened
in that apartment.
Yeah.
Hey, here comes Sam.
Oh, great.
She's gonna see me
in this costume
and insult me 19 different ways.
Too easy.
Wait.
So, Lewbert said
the apartment's haunted?
Pretty much.
Man, now I wanna sneak in there
and check the place out.
Hey, that's perfect.
What?
What's perfect?
Let's do "iCarly" tonight
from apartment 13-B.
No!
Yes!
Come on, Freddie.
Halloween night,
we do a live webcast
from a supposedly
haunted apartment.
I say no.
If only someone
cared what you say.
And what are you, afraid?
No.
I'm just concerned
for Carly's safety.
I'll be fine.
Oh, my God, giant pumpkin.
What do you mean...
whoa, daddy.
Look at that thing.
Big, right?
That's a pumpkin?
Did it grow next door
to a nuclear power plant?
Can we eat it?
My mom makes me dinner,
like, twice a year, okay?
All right.
It's time to carve
the biggest Jack-o'-lantern
of all time.
How do you carve
a pumpkin that big?
Same way I make onion rings.
Stand back!
Hey, "iCarly" starts in an hour.
I'm gonna go put on my costume.
I'm about to hit guts!
Aah!
Come on! Come on!
Let's go!
Don't take this personally!
13-B.
I say this is a bad idea.
Dude, calm down.
No one lives here.
And there's no such
thing as ghosts.
It's locked.
Uh-oh, locked.
Guess we have to do "iCarly"
from our usual studio.
I'm disappointed, but, oh, well.
I have a plan to get us in.
What?
Okay.
Lewbert has keys
to all the apartments, right?
So, I'll go down
to the lobby and fake
like I'm choking on a meatball,
then you and Sam sneak in,
and when Lewbert's
not looking...
We're in.
Never mind.
Here we go.
"ICarly" in a haunted apartment.
Get in there, witchiepoo.
Uh, I have to go
make my mom a salad.
Don't shove! Ow!
Hey, careful!
Sam!
Would you... ah.
Careful!
Where's the light switch?
I got it.
What a dump.
Looks like nobody's
been here for years.
It's creepy.
And it smells like dead bugs.
Can we please not
talk about dead bugs
while I'm wearing this?
All right. Let me establish
a cross-duplex transmission
between my laptop and my camera.
Wow. A tech-talkin' witch boy.
Look out, ladies.
And "iCarly" is live
in five, four, three, two...
Happy Halloween!
Do the scary music.
♪ Ooh whee ooh ♪
Why the scary music?
'Cause tonight,
"iCarly" comes to you
live from an abandoned
apartment...
That people swear is haunted.
So, are there really
such things as ghosts?
And if so, are there ghosts
living in this very apartment?
Do it with me this time.
♪ Ooh whee ooh ♪
Now, we pledge
to stay right here...
In this abandoned apartment...
Webcasting to you
live till midnight...
'Cause we're here to prove...
That you need light
to do a web show.
Freddie,
turn the lights back on.
I didn't turn 'em off.
Freddie.
I swear.
Well, if you didn't,
then who did?
Wait a sec. What happened?
I just felt something on my leg.
Oh, come on, Carly.
Okay, guys.
Quit playing aro...
Get it off me!
Kids and Halloween fun.
Freddie, what are you doing?
I'm setting up the
night vision lens.
Okay, let's see if this works.
Perfect. Everybody watching
can see you guys now.
Okay. It's still Halloween, and
we're webcasting to you live
from an abandoned apartment...
Where things seem
to have taken a turn
for the freaky...
'Cause it looks
like this place may
actually be haunted.
But I doubt it.
Just a little thunder.
Get out!
Go away!
That didn't sound
like thunder, Sam.
Now, can we leave?
We made a pledge to stay.
Get out!
I vote we cancel the pledge.
I second Sam's vote!
Let's bail!
It's not opening!
Come on, just turn the knob!
It won't turn!
Try hitting it with something!
Ow, ow, ow! Not me!
Ow, ow!
Now that is a pile
of pumpkin guts.
Comin'.
Trick or treat.
Hey, how you guys doin' tonight?
Good.
Those are some great costumes.
Just give us the candy.
I see.
Funny story, kids.
You see, I was gonna buy candy
after I carved my
pumpkin, but...
Yeah. We don't care.
Give us treats.
Ow, you're killing me!
Get out! Leave!
Go away!
I will kill you!
All right.
You guys get a six-pack
of diet root beer,
a box of macaroni,
and a pouch of tuna fish.
Happy Halloween!
Stupid door!
Come on!
Open it!
Get out!
We're trying!
Ow! Ow!
The doorknob came off!
Why'd you pull off the doorknob?
'Cause I wanted it
for my knob collection!
Would you guys not fight
in front of the ghost?
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Grow up, Sam!
Okay.
As you know, we pledged to you,
the fans of "iCarly,"
that we will not leave
this apartment
until midnight tonight.
A pledge we will now keep
since Freddie yanked
the knob off the door.
Run to the closet!
Everybody in here?
I'm here.
Here.
Wait, whose butt is this?
Sam.
Sorry.
Trick or treat!
Hey, happy Halloween!
Give us treats.
Well, okay then, Mr. Pushy.
Here's a carton of eggs,
pork chop...
jumper cables!
There you go.
And a coconut. Enjoy.
This isn't candy.
I'm sorry,
I don't have any candy,
but come back next year, okay?
Yeah, we'll be back.
Okay. Freddie is filming me and
Sam as we hide in the closet
of an abandoned apartment...
Which we think is haunted,
if we didn't know
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Yeah, keep hangin'
on to that dream.
I wish we could see in here.
Oh, there's a little light
on my keychain here.
Let me just turn
this baby on and...
Oh, good.
Now we can see in the...
Clown head!
Whoa, that was close.
Hey, why do my hands feel wet?
What's on my hands?
Sam, that's blood!
Blood?
Ew, ew, ew, ew!
Eww, eww, eww, eww!
And there you go.
Enjoy those ice cubes.
All right.
I got to finish this pumpkin.
Comin'.
Macaroni, ice cubes,
and jumper cables?
Okay, look.
I'm not gonna be intimidated
by a bunch of...
Get him!
Whoa!
Aah!
I gotta hide.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I got a noise complaint!
What's going on here?
There's a dude in there
who ticked us off.
We wanna beat him up.
Okey-dokey.
Beat him quietly!
Quietly!
Anybody see him?
Nope.
He's gotta be here somewhere.
Okay, we thought this
would be a cool place
to webcast from on Halloween.
But it turns out this apartment
really is haunted.
This could be the very last
"iCarly" Webcast ever.
And if anything
horrible happens to us...
Mom, I lied to you.
Those pants do
make you look fat.
Die, die, die.
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Mrs. Halberstadt?
What's going on here?
Mother, do you
know these people?
What?
Who are you?
And what are you doing here?
I'm Gary.
I live here.
Huh?
What?
We thought this
apartment was vacant.
No. I've lived here with my
mother for the last 20 years.
Why are you here?
Well, we do this web show.
"ICarly."
I what?
ICarly.
We're kinda doin' it right now.
We heard this place was haunted.
Why do you want a marshmallow?
This apartment isn't haunted.
Then why'd all the lights
go out for no reason?
This switch shorts
out sometimes.
This one works fine.
Why is everyone whispering?
Mother, turn on
your hearing aid.
What?
Better?
You don't have to shout.
She's always forgetting
to turn on her hearing aid.
That explains why
she didn't hear you
in the lobby.
Well, yeah,
but that doesn't explain
why we heard someone screaming,
"Get out! Get out!"
And a bunch of crazy thumping.
Oh, there was an awful
spider in my room,
and I was trying to kill it
with my tennis racket.
Wait.
What did we feel
scratching on our legs?
And what knocked all that
glass stuff off the shelves?
Abigail.
Yes.
Where is she?
Abigail, where are you,
sweetheart?
Oh, there she is.
She's always getting
into mischief.
Who's mommy's wicked,
little pussycat, huh?
Well, explain
the severed clown head
in the closet.
Yeah. What about
the severed clown head?
Yeah.
Severed clown head?
Oh.
It's a phone.
See?
Well, how come
it's not plugged in?
It was.
No one ever called.
Any more questions?
Yeah.
Just before you came home,
your mother walked in saying,
"die, die, die."
Oh, I was just looking
for my red hair dye,
and here it is all spilled out.
So it wasn't blood.
Okay, I guess this apartment
isn't so haunted.
Whoops.
Well, we're sorry we went
in here without permission,
but when we saw
this furniture...
We thought it was
too old and gross
for anyone to actually use.
Oh!
Okay, wait.
Something still
doesn't make sense.
Why did Lewbert tell us
that no one lives here?
'Cause I'm a jerk! Ha!
Ah, I got you kids good.
Score one for Lewbert.
Happy Hanukkah.
Halloween.
We can't find him.
He's gotta be here somewhere.
Maybe he crawled up the...
Socko, this is not
a good time to call.
He's in the pumpkin!
No, I'm not!
I am the spirit of Halloween!
Pumpkin noises.
Open the elevator!
Ah!
Help me push him in!
Come on, guys, stop rolling me!
Where's your Halloween spirit!
Hey.
What are you kids doing
with that pumpkin?
There's a dude in here!
We're gonna roll
it down the street.
And into the ocean.
Happy Hannukah.
Stop!
The spirit
of Halloween can't swim!
No, no, no, no!
Not into the traffic!
No!
Get out!
So this wasn't exactly
a normal "iCarly" webcast.
But it was kind of wacky.
Perhaps too wacky.
Yet very Halloweeny.
And now we're done.
Don't forget to keep
comin' back to iCarly.com
and checkin' out our site.
And be sure to check out...
And this is Carly's brother,
Spencer.
Any words for our viewers
before we sign off?
Never forget to buy
candy on Halloween.
Hi, I'm William.
And I'm Tommy.
We're twin brothers,
but we're nothing alike.
We're gonna demonstrate a thing
called sports stacking.
I'm the left hand.
And I'm the right hand.
All right, let's go.
And there you have it,
sports stacking.
We love you, Carly.
We love you, Sam.
And you, too, Freddie.